[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How did James Bonds parents die?", "correct_answer": "Climbing accident", "incorrect_answers": ["Executed", "Plane crash", "Drowned"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What spice possesses antidepressant properties?", "correct_answer": "Saffron", "incorrect_answers": ["Black pepper", "Chilli", "Nutmeg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following gets shot when Bart arrives in Rock Ridge in the film Blazing Saddles?", "correct_answer": "A Bible", "incorrect_answers": ["The Church Bell", "Barts Hat", "The Clock tower"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of food does the guinea pig naturally feed on?", "correct_answer": "Grass", "incorrect_answers": ["Grains", "Green leaved", "Nuts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following words is a synonym of paraskevidekatriaphobia (fear of Friday the 13th)?", "correct_answer": "Friggatriskaidekaphobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Aphenphosmphobia", "Triskaidekaphobia", "Arachnophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What rating did the Motion Picture Association of America give to the 2007 hit movie 300?", "correct_answer": "R", "incorrect_answers": ["PG-13", "NC-17", "PG"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This English author, whose works include An Essay on Criticism and The Rape of the Lock, directly addressed the major religious, political and intellectual problems of the 18th century.", "correct_answer": "Alexander Pope", "incorrect_answers": ["Ben Johnson", "Jonathan Swift", "Samuel Johnson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chipmunks are small squirrel-like rodents belonging to the genus Tamias. What does the Greek word tamias mean?", "correct_answer": "Storer", "incorrect_answers": ["Nibbler", "Squirrel", "Stripes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is Saint Nicolas the patron saint of sailors and merchants in Eastern Orthodox countries?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what Manhattan neighbourhood did the boys in the movie Sleepers live?", "correct_answer": "Hells Kitchen", "incorrect_answers": ["Heavens Kitchen", "Heaven Lounge room", "Hells Lounge room"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do most bat species spend the cold winter months?", "correct_answer": "They hibernate.", "incorrect_answers": ["They migrate south to to regions with warmer climates.", "They do not change their behavior in the winter.", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the 2007 smash hit Transformers?", "correct_answer": "Michael Bay", "incorrect_answers": ["George Lucas", "James Cameron", "John Turteltaub"]}]